Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004
Duke University. University Archives
- Addition, 2004 [A2004-19] (Box 60)
  - Faculty and staff (Box 60)
    - deButts, John D. [Duke Endowment Trustee] (Box 70)
    - Dees, Greg [Fuqua], 2001 (Box 70)
    - Dees, John Essary [Urology], d.5/19/1993 (Box 70)
    - deJuan, Eugene, Jr. [Ophthalmology] (Box 70)
    - De La Paz, Monica [Ophthalmology] (Box 70)
    - Dell, Diana [Obstetrics and Gynecology] (Box 70)
    - Dellinger, David Carol [Fuqua] (Box 70)
    - Dellinger, Walter E., III [Law ], 1980-2001 (Box 71)
    - Delong, G. Robert [Pediatric Neurology] (Box 71)
    - DeLong, Mark [TIP] (Box 71)
    - De Lucia, Frank C. [Physics] (Box 71)
    - de Marchi, Neil Barry [Economics] (Box 71)
    - DeMaria, William J. A. [Pediatrics] (Box 71)
    - Demark-Wahnefried, Wendy [DUMC], 1998 (Box 71)
    - DeMik, Harry E. [Deputy University Registrar] (Box 71)
    - DeRuyter, Frank [Speech Pathology and Audiology], 1998 (Box 71)
    - DeMott, Deborah A. [Law ] (Box 71)
    - DeNeef, A. Leigh [English] (Box 71)
    - Dennis, Vincent W. [Nephrology, DUMC] (Box 71)
    - Dent, Sara Jamison [Anesthesiology] (Box 71)
    - Denzin, Lisa Kae [Immunology] (Box 71)
    - DeSanctis, Gerardine [Fuqua] (Box 71)
    - Desmond, Jane Carol [Dance Program] (Box 71)
    - Detomo, Paul M. (Box 71)
    - De Vitto, John (Box 71)
    - De Vries, William [Duke Intern - performed 1st artificial heart implant] (Box 71)
    - de Vyver, Frank Traver [Economics], d.5/11/1980 (Box 71)
    - Dewey, Allen [Electrical and Computer Engineering], d. 12/17/1999 (Box 71)
    - Dewhirst, Mark [Radiation Oncology] (Box 71)
    - Diamond, Irving T. [Psychology] (Box 71)
    - Di Bona, Joseph [Education] (Box 71)
    - Di Cecco, Luca [Cello] (Box 71)
    - Dickens, Robert Louis [Fuqua] (Box 71)
    - Dickson, Sally M. [Institutional Equity] (Box 71)
    - Dickerson, Janet Smith [Student Affairs] (Box 71)
    - Di Giulio, Richard T. [NSOE] (Box 71)
    - Di Prete, Thomas A. [Sociology] (Box 71)
    - Dirlik, Arif [History] (Box 71)
    - Dittman, Jane (Box 71)
    - Dixon, Thomas E. (Box 71)
    - Dodd, Stephen Howard [Asian and African Languages] (Box 71)
    - Dodge, Kenneth [Public Policy] (Box 71)
    - Dodson, William C. [Endocrinology and Infertility] (Box 71)
    - Dolan, Edward A. [Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery] (Box 71)
    - Dollas, Apostolos [Electrical Engineering / Computer Science] (Box 71)
    - Dominguez, Virginia Rosa [Anthropology] (Box 71)
    - Donatucci, Craig F. [Urology] (Box 71)
    - Donelan, William J. [Medical Center Administration] (Box 71)
    - Doraiswamy, Murali [Psychiatry] (Box 71)
    - Doran, Diane M. [Biological Anthropology and Anatomy] (Box 71)
    - Dorfman, Ariel, 1980-2000 (Box 71)
    - Dorr, Darwin [Psychology] (Box 72)
    - Douglass, Fenner [Music], Retired 10/31/1987 (Box 72)
    - Douthat, James Evans (Box 72)
    - Dovenmuehle, Robert H. [Psychiatry] (Box 72)
    - Dowell, Earl H. [Engineering] (Box 72)
    - Doyle, Roger W. [Ecology] (Box 72)
    - Dozier, John Marion (Box 72)
    - Drake, Ralph Lendon [DUMC] (Box 72)
    - Drezner, Marc Kenneth (Box 72)
    - Dronsfield, James B. [Information Technology] (Box 72)
    - D'Sousa, Bernard J. [Pediatric Neurology] (Box 72)
    - Dugan, Eugene K. (Box 72)
    - Dugan, Joanne Bechta [Computer Science] (Box 72)
    - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing (Box 72)
    - Duncan, Pamela W. [Endocrinology] (Box 72)
    - Dunlap, Susan J. [Divinity] (Box 72)
    - Dunn, Frederick L [Endocrinology] (Box 72)
    - Dunn, Patrick P. [History] (Box 72)
    - Dunn, Susan [Music] (Box 72)
    - Dunnick, N. Reed [Radiology] (Box 72)
    - Dunning, Arthur Stephenson, Jr. "Stephen" (Box 72)
    - Dupree, Louis [Public Policy], d. 3/21/1989 (Box 72)
    - Durack, David Tulloch [Infectious Diseases] (Box 72)
    - Durden, Robert F. [History] (Box 72)
    - Durham, William Harry (Box 72)
    - Dutrow, George F. [NSOE] (Box 72)
    - Dutton, John Austin [Aerospace Studies] (Box 72)
    - Dutton, Jonathan J. [Ophthalmology] (Box 72)
    - Dyer, Allen Ralph [Psychiatry] (Box 72)
    - Dykstra, Craig (Box 72)
    - Eaker, Mark Robbe (Box 72)
    - Eakin, Frank Edwin, Jr. [Religion] (Box 72)
    - Earle, Ralph, Jr. (Box 72)
    - Earls, Paul [Music] (Box 72)
    - Ebert, Harry Frederick (Box 72)
    - Ebert, Paul A. (Box 72)
    - Eckerman, Carol O. [Psychology] (Box 72)
    - Eckert, Edward (Box 72)
    - Eddy, David, 1962-1989 (Box 72)
    - Eddy, Ruth Bochanan (Box 72)
    - Edeburn, Judson D. (Box 72)
    - Edell, Julie A. [Fuqua] (Box 72)
    - Edelsbrunner, Herbert [Computer Science], 2000 (Box 72)
    - Edie, Fred [Divinity], 2001 (Box 72)
    - Edinger, Jack [Medical Psychology] (Box 72)
    - Edmonds, Thomas A. (Box 72)
    - Edwards, Glenn [Physics] (Box 72)
    - Edwards, Herbert O. [Divinity School] (Box 72)
    - Edwards, Joe (Box 72)
    - Effman, Eric Leonard [Radiology and Anatomy] (Box 72)
    - Efird, James Michael "Mickey" [Divinity School] (Box 72)
    - Eisendorfer, Carl [Medical Psychology] (Box 73)
    - Eisenbud, Merrill (Box 73)
    - Eisenhardt, William [Naval ROTC] (Box 73)
    - Eldridge, Albert F. [Political Science; TCAS] (Box 73)
    - Elion, Gertrude Belle (Box 73)
    - Ellenbogen, Charles (Box 73)
    - Ellinwood, Everett Hews, Jr. [Psychiatry] (Box 73)
    - Elliott, William Whitfield [Mathematics ] (Box 73)
    - Ellis, Carla Schlatter [Computer Science] (Box 73)
    - Ellis, George J., III [Endocrinology] (Box 73)
    - Ellis, Leon Hubbard [Political Science] (Box 73)
    - Ellis, Matthew [Oncology], 2001 (Box 73)
    - Ellis, Rene [Law] (Box 73)
    - Elsevier, Ernest [Mechanical Engineering], d. 4/10/2002 (Box 73)
    - Elwell, Stanley William [DUMC] (Box 73)
    - Embree, Ainslie T. [History] (Box 73)
    - Endow, Sharyn Anne [Microbiology and Immunology] (Box 73)
    - Engler, Mark J. (Box 73)
    - English, Peter Calvin (Box 73)
    - Ennis, Alana [Police Duke University] (Box 73)
    - Entman, Robert M. [Public Policy] (Box 73)
    - Entwhistle, Richard R. (Box 73)
    - Enzer, Norbert B. [Psychiatry; Pediatrics] (Box 73)
    - Epstein, Ann W. [Art and Art History], 1986 (Box 73)
    - Epstein, David L. [Ophthalmology; Duke Eye Center] (Box 73)
    - Erickson, Carl John [Psychology] (Box 73)
    - Erickson, Harold P. [Cell Biology] (Box 73)
    - Erickson, Robert Porter [Psychology] (Box 73)
    - Erwin, C. William (Box 73)
    - Erwin, William R., Jr. [Perkins Library] (Box 73)
    - Escueta, Antonio V. (Box 73)
    - Esser, Cary (Box 73)
    - Estes, Edward Harvey, Jr. [Community and Family Medicine] (Box 73)
    - Estes, Kenneth W. [Naval Science] (Box 73)
    - Ettin, Edward C. (Box 73)
    - Eubanks, Georgann [Continuing Education] (Box 73)
    - Eubanks, Steve [Endosurgical Education] (Box 73)
    - Evans, John C. [Radiology ] (Box 73)
    - Evans, Lawrence Eugene [Physics] (Box 73)
    - Everett, John W. [Anatomy], Retired 8/31/1976 (Box 73)
    - Everett, Robinson Oscar [Law], 1960-2000 (Box 73)
    - Ewald, Wendy [Center for Documentary Studies] (Box 73)
    - Ewing, Katherine [Cultural Anthropology] (Box 73)
    - Eyerman, William Penn [Admissions] (Box 73)
    - Eyuboglu, B. Murat [Biomedical Engineering] (Box 73)
    - Fair, Richard Barton [Electrical Engineering] (Box 73)
    - Fairbank, Henry A. [Physics], Retired 8/31/1988 (Box 73)
    - Faksh, Mahmud A. [Political Science] (Box 73)
    - Falcone, David J. (Box 73)
    - Falletta, John Matthew [Oncology; Pediatrics] (Box 73)
    - Farber, Jonathan M. [Clinical Psychology] (Box 73)
    - Farley, W. Reynolds [Sociology] (Box 73)
    - Farmer, Joseph C., Jr. [Otolaryngology] (Box 73)
    - Farquhar, Michelle C. [University Trustee] (Box 73)
    - Farris, Donn Michael [Divinity School Library] (Box 73)
    - Faust, Bruce C. [NSOE] (Box 73)
    - Feather, Ben W. [Psychiatry] (Box 73)
    - Feagin, John [Orthopedic Surgery] (Box 73)
    - Feaver, Peter Douglas [Political Science], 2001 (Box 73)
    - Feenberg, Andrew Lewis [Philosophy] (Box 73)
    - Fehon, Richard G. [Zoology] (Box 73)
    - Fein, John Morton [Romance Languages] (Box 73)
    - Feinglos, Mark N. [Endocrinology] (Box 73)
    - Feldman, Jerome M. [Endocrinology] (Box 73)
    - Felsman, Kirk [Public Policy] (Box 73)
    - Felton, Gayle Carlton [Divinity School] (Box 73)
    - Fendt, Paul F. (Box 73)
    - Ferejohn, Michael T. [Philosophy] (Box 73)
    - Ferguson, Arthur B. [History], Effective 9/31/1983 (Box 73)
    - Ferguson, Charles E. [Mathematical Economics] (Box 73)
    - Ferguson, John F. [Pratt], 2002 (Box 73)
    - Ferguson, Oliver Watkins [English] (Box 73)
    - Ferraro, Thomas Joseph [English] (Box 73)
    - Ferriero, David [University Librarian] (Box 73)
    - Ferree-Clark, Nancy [Duke Chapel] (Box 73)
    - Ferrell, Ron P. [University Photographer] (Box 73)
    - Fetter, Bernard Frank [Pathology] (Box 73)
    - Feussner, John R. [DUMC and VA Med. Ctr.] (Box 73)
    - Fielding, Sara [Romance Languages] (Box 73)
    - Fierke, Carol [Biochemistry] (Box 73)
    - Filston, Howard C. [Thoracic and Pediatric Surgery] (Box 73)
    - Fine, Robert Lance [Medicine and Pharmacology] (Box 73)
    - Finger, Joseph Michael [Economics] (Box 73)
    - Finucci, Valeria [Romance Languages] (Box 73)
    - Fish, Peter G. (Box 73)
    - Fish, Stanley Eugene [English], 1985-2000 (Box 73)
    - Fischer, Karla [Law and Psychology] (Box 74)
    - Fisher, Albert [Divinity] (Box 74)
    - Fisher, John H. [English] (Box 74)
    - Fishman, Sue Horan [Student Activities] (Box 74)
    - Fitch, Robert D. [Orthopedic Surgery] (Box 74)
    - Fitz, John G. [Medicine] (Box 74)
    - Fitzgerald, Michael [Chemistry] (Box 74)
    - Fitzpatrick, David [Anatomy] (Box 74)
    - Flanagan, Owen [Philosophy] (Box 74)
    - Flath, Daniel Evans [Physics] (Box 74)
    - Fleishman, Joel Lawrence, 1971-2001 (Box 74)
    - Flowers, Maxine Rogers [Psychiatric Social Work] (Box 74)
    - Floyd, Walter Lawrence [Cardiology] (Box 74)
    - Fluke, Donald J. [Zoology] (Box 74)
    - Fogleman, Paul (Box 74)
    - Folger, Fred (Box 74)
    - Folz, Rodney J. [Pulmonary Medicine] (Box 74)
    - Forbus, Wiley D. [Pathology], Retired 9/1/1964; d. 3/3/1976 (Box 74)
    - Forlines, John Arthur (Box 74)
    - Fortier, Kenneth J. [Obstetrics and Gynecology] (Box 74)
    - Forsyth, John D. [Fuqua] (Box 74)
    - Fortin, Donald [Cardiology] (Box 74)
    - Fortney, Lloyd Ray [Physics], d.3/7/1999 (Box 74)
    - Forton, Gerald T. [Dietary Services, DUMC] (Box 74)
    - Fortune, Ellen G. [Nursing] (Box 74)
    - Forward, Richard B., Jr. [Biology/Zoology, Marine Lab., Beaufort] (Box 74)
    - Foster, Andrew Durwood, Jr. [Divinity School] (Box 74)
    - Foster, C. Allen [Law] (Box 74)
    - Foster, Darrell V. [Computer Science] (Box 74)
    - Foster, F. Douglas [Fuqua] (Box 74)
    - Foster, Ludmila Alexandrovna [Slavic Languages] (Box 74)
    - Foster, William L. [Radiology] (Box 74)
    - Foulks, Gary Neal [Ophthalmology] (Box 74)
    - Fousek, Marianka K. [Religion] (Box 74)
    - Fouts, Nevin [Fuqua], 1999 (Box 74)
    - Fowler, Donald R. [Psychiatry] (Box 74)
    - Fowler, Earle Cabell [Physics] (Box 74)
    - Fowler, Edward Blair [Center for International Studies] (Box 74)
    - Fowler, John A. [Psychiatry] (Box 74)
    - Fowlie, Wallace [French Literature], d. 8/16/1998 (Box 74)
    - Fowlkes, H. Lee (Box 74)
    - Fox, Elisabeth June [Clinical Anesthesiology] (Box 74)
    - Fox. James Joseph [Anthropology] (Box 74)
    - Fox, Richard G. [Anthropology] (Box 74)
    - Frances, Allen [Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences] (Box 74)
    - Francis, Garrick Codrington [Office of Government Relations and Community Affairs] (Box 74)
    - Francis, Jennifer [Fuqua] (Box 74)
    - Frank, Gerald D. [Music] (Box 74)
    - Frank, Michael M. [Pediatrics] (Box 74)
    - Franks, Carl [Head Football Coach] (Box 74)
    - Franzoni, Linda [Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science] (Box 74)
    - Fraser-Reid, Bertram Oliver [Chemistry] (Box 74)
    - Frederick, Donald G. (Box 74)
    - Fredrickson, Barbara L. (Box 74)
    - Freedman, Jonathan H. [NSOE] (Box 74)
    - Freeman, Curtis [Divinity], 2001 (Box 74)
    - Freeman, Jay N. (Box 74)
    - Freemark, Michael [Endocrinology, Pediatrics ] (Box 74)
    - Freetag, William P. (Box 74)
    - French, John [History] (Box 74)
    - Frenzel, Charles H. [DUMC] (Box 74)
    - Frey, Kip [Fuqua], 2001 (Box 74)
    - Fridovich, Irwin [Biochemistry] (Box 74)
    - Friedberg, Ruth (Box 74)
    - Friedl, Ernestine [TCAS; Anthropology] (Box 74)
    - Friedman, Allan Howard [Neurosurgery], 2001 (Box 74)
    - Friedman, Henry S. [Hematology, Oncology, Pediatrics; Pathology] (Box 74)
    - Friedman, Nancy E. [Endocrinology, Pediatrics] (Box 74)
    - Friedrich, John A. [Health, P. E. and Recreation Dept.] (Box 74)
    - Frothingham, Thomas Eliot [Pediatrics] (Box 74)
    - Fuchs, Herbert E. [Neurosurgery; Asst Pediatrics] (Box 74)
    - Fulkerson, Mary McClintock [Divinity School] (Box 74)
    - Fulkerson, William J., Jr. [DUMC and Duke PDC] (Box 74)
    - Fuller, J. Peyton [Planning and Analysis and Univ. Treasurer] (Box 74)
    - Fulton, Charles Darby, Jr. [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 74)
    - Fultz, Saylor J. (Jim) [Controller of General Accounts] (Box 74)
    - Funderburk, M. Laney [Alumni Affairs] (Box 74)
    - Fuqua, John Brooks (Box 74)
    - Furbish, William James, Retired 3/1/1983 (Box 74)
    - Futhey, Tracy [Information Technology], 2001 (Box 74)
    - Futreal, Andrew [Molecular Geneticist] (Box 74)
    - Gadde, Kishore [Clinical Psychiatry] (Box 74)
    - Gaede, Jane Taylor [Clinical Pathology] (Box 74)
    - Gaines, Jane Marie [English] (Box 74)
    - Gallagher, John P. [Computer Education Center, Fuqua] (Box 74)
    - Gallie, Thomas Muir [Computer Science] (Box 74)
    - Gallis, Harry Anthony [Infectious Diseases] (Box 74)
    - Gan, Tong Joo [Anesthesiology] (Box 74)
    - Gann, Pamela B. [and Law] (Box 74)
    - Gao, Bai [Sociology], 1998 (Box 74)
    - Garbutt, John T., Jr. [Gastroenterology] (Box 74)
    - Garci-Gomaz, Miguel [Romance Languages] (Box 74)
    - Garcia-Blanco, Mariano [Pharm. and Cancer Bio; Microbio.; Res. of Medicine] (Box 74)
    - Gardner, Carl L. [Computer Science] (Box 74)
    - Gardner, Clarence E., Jr. [Surgery] (Box 74)
    - Gardner, Grant W. [Fuqua] (Box 74)
    - Gardner, William H. [Civil Engineering] (Box 74)
    - Garg, Davendra P. [Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science] (Box 74)
    - Garrett, William E. [Orthopedic Surgery] (Box 74)
    - Garrison, Edwin R. [Divinity School] (Box 74)
    - Garson, Arthur "Tim," Jr. [Pediatric Cardiology; Health Affairs] (Box 74)
    - Garst, Jennifer [Oncology] (Box 74)
    - Gaspar, David Barry [History] (Box 74)
    - Gates, Henry Louis "Skip," Jr. [English] (Box 74)
    - Gauthier, Daniel J. [Physics] (Box 74)
    - Gavins, Raymond [History] (Box 74)
    - Gay, Francis Norman "Frank" [Personnel, DUMC], 1967 (Box 74)
    - Geer, Bennett E. [Endowment Trustee], Effective 12/11/1924 (Box 75)
    - Gehman, W. Scott [Psychology, Education] (Box 75)
    - Geist, Robert M., III [Computer Science] (Box 75)
    - Gelenbe, Erol [Electrical and Computer Engineering] (Box 75)
    - Gelfand, Alan [Stats and Decision Sciences] (Box 75)
    - Geller, Henry [Public Policy] (Box 75)
    - Geller, Matthew M. [Computer Science] (Box 75)
    - Gellhorn, Ernest A. E. [Law] (Box 75)
    - George, Linda Kay Kaufman [Psychiatry] (Box 75)
    - George, Rhett T., Jr. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 75)
    - George, Timothy [Neurosurgery], 1998 (Box 75)
    - Georgiade, Gregory S. [Gen. and Thoracic Surgery, and Plastic Surgery] (Box 75)
    - Georgiade, Nicholas [Plastic Surgery] (Box 75)
    - Gerber, Linda H. [Alumni Affairs and Univ. Development] (Box 75)
    - Gereffi, Gary [Sociology], 2001 (Box 75)
    - Gergen, David [Public Policy] (Box 75)
    - Geweke, John F. [Economics; Stats and Decision Sciences] (Box 75)
    - Gewirth, Daniel Tilton [Biochemistry] (Box 75)
    - Gheith, Jehanne [Slavic Dept. ] (Box 75)
    - Ghiradelli, Robert G. [Chemistry] (Box 75)
    - Gianturco, Daniel T. [Psychiatry; Medical Education] (Box 75)
    - Giddings, Pauls [Women's/African and African American Studies] (Box 75)
    - Gifford, James Fergus, Jr. [DUMC Archivist] (Box 75)
    - Gilbert, Allan H. [English], d. 4/26/1987 (Box 75)
    - Gilbert, Paula E. [Divinity School] (Box 75)
    - Gilboa, Eli [DUMC], 2001 (Box 75)
    - Gilgor, Robert E. [Dermatology] (Box 75)
    - Gillin, Donald G. [History] (Box 75)
    - Gilkeson, Gary [Arthritis Center] (Box 75)
    - Gillespie, Michael Allen [Political Science] (Box 75)
    - Gillham, Nicholas W. [Zoology] (Box 75)
    - Gilliam, Bryan [Music] (Box 75)
    - Gillis, Stephen Malcolm [Public Policy; Vice Provost, Academic Affairs; Graduate School] (Box 75)
    - Ginsberg, Brian [Anesthesiology] (Box 75)
    - Gionta, Ralph Lawrence [Planning Manager, Physical Plant], Retired 6/1987 (Box 75)
    - Gittler, Joseph B. [Sociology] (Box 75)
    - Glander, Kenneth Earl [Biological Anthropology and Anatomy; Primate Center] (Box 75)
    - Glass, Peter [Anesthesiology] (Box 75)
    - Glasson, John [Consulting Surgery] (Box 75)
    - Gleckner, Robert F. [English] (Box 75)
    - Glenn, James Francis [Urology] (Box 75)
    - Glenn, Thomas M. [Health Affairs] (Box 75)
    - Glover-Wetherington, Miriam Anne [Divinity School] (Box 75)
    - Glower, Donald [Thoracic Surgery] (Box 75)
    - Godwin, David J. [Transfusion Services Hemotherapy] (Box 75)
    - Godwin, Harold L. [Medicine] (Box 75)
    - Goestenkors, Gail [Women's Basketball Coach] (Box 75)
    - Gohdes, Clarence Louis Frank [English] (Box 75)
    - Gold, Deborah [Research Psychology and Behavioral Science; Sociology] (Box 75)
    - Goldberg, Mary Lucile "Marylu" [Psychology], d. 2001 (Box 75)
    - Goldberg, Ronald [Neonatal-Perinatal Medicine, DUMC] (Box 75)
    - Golding, Martin P. [Philosophy and Law; Philosophy Dept. ] (Box 75)
    - Goldner, J. Leonard [Orthopedic Surgery] (Box 75)
    - Goldner, Richard D. [Orthopedic Surgery] (Box 75)
    - Goldschmidt, Pascal J. [Neurosurgery], 2001 (Box 75)
    - Goldsmith, Fred [Head Football Coach] (Box 75)
    - Goldstein, Larry [Neurologist; Duke's Center for Cerebrovascular Disease] (Box 75)
    - Goldwater, Leonard J. [Founder, Occupational Medicine], d. 7/2/1992 (Box 75)
    - Golner, Geoffrey Robinson [Physics] (Box 75)
    - Goodson, W. Kenneth [Bishop, UMC; Trustee, Univ. and Endowment; Divinity Sch. Board of Visitors], d. 9/17/1991 (Box 75)
    - Goodwin, Crauford David W. [Economics. Grad. Sch.; Vice Provost for Research] (Box 75)
    - Goodwyn, Lawrence Corbett [History] (Box 75)
    - Gopen, George D. [English; Writing Programs] (Box 75)
    - Gordon, Alexander [Therapeutic Recreation Coordinator, Pediatric Units Support Service] (Box 75)
    - Gordon, Andrew [History] (Box 75)
    - Gosele, Ulrich M. [Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science] (Box 75)
    - Goshaw, Alfred T. [Physics] (Box 75)
    - Gotwals, Harry D. [Vice President] (Box 75)
    - Grabowski, Henry George [Economics; Economics ( 9/1989 - 8/1992)] (Box 75)
    - Grady, Tana [Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences; Medicine] (Box 75)
    - Graffagnino, Carmello [Co-Neuro Critical Care Unit] (Box 75)
    - Graham, Daniel A. [Economics] (Box 75)
    - Graham, Doyle Gene [Pathology; Medical Education] (Box 75)
    - Graham, James Douglas [Instructor, History] (Box 75)
    - Graham, John R. [Fuqua], 1999 (Box 75)
    - Graham, John W. [Planning] (Box 75)
    - Grandin, Greg [History], 2000 (Box 75)
    - Grandis, Arnold [Perinatology] (Box 75)
    - Granger, Christopher [Cardiologist, Duke's Clinical Research Institute (DCRI)] (Box 75)
    - Grant, Augustus O. [Cardiology] (Box 75)
    - Grant, John P. [General and Thoracic Surgery] (Box 75)
    - Grant, Richard Babson [Romance Languages] (Box 75)
    - Grant, Ruth [Political Science], 2001 (Box 75)
    - Gratz, Pauline [Nursing], Retired 9/1/1985 (Box 75)
    - Gray, C. Jarrett, Jr. [Divinity School] (Box 75)
    - Gray, Irving E. [Zoology; Marine Lab] (Box 75)
    - Greeley, William J. [Anesthesiology; Pediatrics] (Box 76)
    - Green, Monica H. [History] (Box 76)
    - Green, Capt. Richard F. [Commanding Officer, NROTC; Naval Science] (Box 76)
    - Green, Robert L., Jr. [Psychiatry] (Box 76)
    - Green, Warner Craig [Rheumatology and Immunology] (Box 76)
    - Green, William L., Jr. [Public Relations], Retired 12/30/1986 (Box 76)
    - Greenberg, Charles S. [Medicine; Pathology] (Box 76)
    - Greenberg, Michael L. [Res. General Surgery] (Box 76)
    - Greenfield, Joseph C., Jr. [Medicine] (Box 76)
    - Greengrass, Roy A. [Anesthesiology] (Box 76)
    - Greenhill, Maurice H. (Box 76)
    - Greenleaf, Arno L. [Biochemistry] (Box 76)
    - Greenside, Henry [Computer Science; Physics] (Box 76)
    - Greenwood, Joseph A. [Mathematics] (Box 76)
    - Gregg, John Richard [Zoology] (Box 76)
    - Gregg, Robert Allen [Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation] (Box 76)
    - Gregg, Robert C. [Divinity School] (Box 76)
    - Greggs, Gilbert A., Jr. [Divinity School] (Box 76)
    - Grichnik, James M. [Dermatology] (Box 76)
    - Grichnik, Katherine [DUMC], 2000 (Box 76)
    - Grieco, Joseph M. [Political Science], 2001 (Box 76)
    - Griffin, George (Box 76)
    - Griffith, William Jackson, III [Student Affairs] (Box 76)
    - Griffiths, Phillip A. [Mathematics] (Box 76)
    - Grimson, Keith Sanford [Surgery], Retired 7/31/1976; d. 12/14/1988 (Box 76)
    - Grinstaff, Mark [Chemistry] (Box 76)
    - Grislis, Egil [Historical Theology] (Box 76)
    - Grocott, Hilary Peter [Anesthesiology], 2001 (Box 76)
    - Gronke, Paul [Political Science] (Box 76)
    - Gross, Samson Richard [Biochemistry] (Box 76)
    - Grossman, Herman [Radiology; Pediatrics] (Box 76)
    - Grout, Julia Rebecca [Physical Education; First of P. E. Woman's College] (Box 76)
    - Grufferman, Seymour [Clinical Epidemiology, Pediatrics; Prevention and Control, Comprehensive Cancer Center] (Box 76)
    - Guilak, Farshid [Orthopedic Surgery and Research; Biomedical Engineering], 2001 (Box 76)
    - Guild, Walter R. [Biophysics], Effective 1/1/1987 (Box 76)
    - Gulick, Floyd (Box 76)
    - Gunnells, James Caulie, Jr. [Nephrology, Medicine] (Box 76)
    - Gut, Allan [Mathematics] (Box 76)
    - Gutknecht, John [Physiology] (Box 76)
    - Gutman, Laura T. [Duke Univ. Child Protection Team; Pediatric Physician] (Box 76)
    - Guttentag, Christoph O. [Undergraduate Admissions] (Box 76)
    - Guyer, Robert A. [Physics] (Box 76)
    - Guzeldere, Guven [Philosophy] (Box 76)
    - Guzzardi, Peter [Duke Press] (Box 76)
    - Gwyther, Lisa P. [Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development] (Box 76)
    - Haagen, Paul H. [Law] (Box 76)
    - Haas, William Elmer (Box 76)
    - Habig, Robert L. [Pathology] (Box 76)
    - Hackel, Donald Benjamin [Pathology], Retired 8/1/1989; d. 6/1994 (Box 76)
    - Hacker, Herbert, Jr. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 76)
    - Hacohen, Malachi H. [History] (Box 76)
    - Haff, Peter K. [Civil Engineering and Geology] (Box 76)
    - Hagan, Robert Douglas [NROTC] (Box 76)
    - Hage, Marvin L. [Perinatology, Obstetrics and Gynecology] (Box 76)
    - Hagler, Ellis P. [Varsity Football Line Coach; Head Golf Coach], Retired 8/31/1973 (Box 76)
    - Haglund, Michael M. [Neurosurgery] (Box 76)
    - Haines, Howard N. [Civil Engineering], Retired 8/31/1965 (Box 76)
    - Hall, Amy Laura [Divinity] (Box 76)
    - Hall, Elmer O. [Religious Activities; Chaplain] (Box 76)
    - Hall, Frank G. [Physiology and Pharmacology] (Box 76)
    - Hall, Hugh M., Jr. [Political Science] (Box 76)
    - Hall, Kenneth Charles [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 76)
    - Hall, Kenneth Daland [Anesthesiology; Blood Gas Lab.] (Box 76)
    - Hall, Louise [Art] (Box 76)
    - Hall, Russell P., III [Dermatology, Medicine] (Box 76)
    - Hall, Stanford R. (Box 76)